Connect with us

TechBurner
----------

    * [
        
        Top 5 Smartphones Under 30000 In India \[JULY 2022\]](https://techburner.in/top-5-smartphones-under-30000/)
    * [
        
        Best Methods to Get Free Fire Max Diamonds For Free](https://techburner.in/best-methods-to-get-free-fire-max-diamonds-for-free/)
    * [
        
        Best Phones Under 20000 For Gaming](https://techburner.in/best-phones-under-20000-for-gaming/)
    * [
        
        Android 13 Beta 3 Release: Here’s Everything We know!](https://techburner.in/android-13-beta-3-release-heres-everything-we-know/)
    * [
        
        How To Pin Posts On Instagram \[Steps\]](https://techburner.in/how-to-pin-posts-on-instagram-steps/)

    * [
        
        Subscription Based Telegram Premium to Arrive This Month](https://techburner.in/subscription-based-telegram-premium-to-arrive-this-month/)
    * [
        
        Top 5 Windows Apps That You Should Try](https://techburner.in/top-5-windows-apps-that-you-should-try/)
    * [
        
        Best FPS Settings for Apex Legends Mobile](https://techburner.in/best-fps-settings-for-apex-legends-mobile/)
    * [
        
        5 Tips to Reach Heroic Rank or Above in Free Fire MAX](https://techburner.in/5-tips-to-reach-heroic-rank-or-above-in-free-fire-max/)
    * [
        
        Free Fire MAX vs Apex Legends Mobile: Which One is Better?](https://techburner.in/free-fire-max-vs-apex-legends-mobile-which-one-is-better/)

    * [
        
        Google Pixel 7, 7 Pro Stock Wallpapers Download](https://techburner.in/google-pixel-7-7-pro-stock-wallpapers-download/)
    * [
        
        Apple iPhone 14, 14 Plus, 14 Pro, 14 Pro Max Stock Wallpapers Download for Free](https://techburner.in/apple-iphone-14-14-plus14-pro14-pro-max-stock-wallpapers-download-for-free/)
    * [
        
        Download Tecno Camon 19 Pro Stock Wallpapers Now](https://techburner.in/download-tecno-camon-19-pro-stock-wallpapers-now/)
    * [
        
        Download MacOS Ventura Stock Wallpapers Now](https://techburner.in/download-macos-ventura-stock-wallpapers-now/)
    * [
        
        Download iPadOS 16 Stock Wallpapers Now](https://techburner.in/download-ipados-16-stock-wallpapers-now/)

    * [
        
        Best 5G Smartphones Under 20000 in India](https://techburner.in/best-5g-smartphones-under-20000-in-india/)
    * [
        
        Google Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Launched](https://techburner.in/google-pixel-7-and-pixel-7-pro-launched/)
    * [
        
        Top 5 Mobiles Under 20000 in India \[JULY 2022\]](https://techburner.in/top-5-mobiles-under-20000-in-india-july-2022/)
    * [
        
        Methods to Install Android 13 Beta 3.3 on Google Pixel Phones \[GUIDE\]](https://techburner.in/install-android-13-beta-3-3-on-google-pixel-phones/)
    * [
        
        Best Gaming Phone Under 8000 in India](https://techburner.in/best-gaming-phone-under-8000-in-india/)

        * [
            
            MIUI 14 Announced : What’s New, Features, and Devices List](https://techburner.in/miui-14-announced-whats-new-features-and-devices-list/)
        * [
            
            Android 13 Whats New – Everything you Need to Know](https://techburner.in/android-13-whats-new-everything-you-need-to-know/)
        * [
            
            Methods to Install Android 13 Beta 3.3 on Google Pixel Phones \[GUIDE\]](https://techburner.in/install-android-13-beta-3-3-on-google-pixel-phones/)
        * [
            
            How To Download iOS 16 Beta \[Guide\]](https://techburner.in/how-to-download-ios-16-beta-guide/)
        * [
            
            Android 13 Beta 2 GSI on Any Smartphone: Download and Install \[With Links\]](https://techburner.in/android-13-beta-2-gsi-on-any-smartphone-download-and-install-with-links/)

    * [
        
        Poco F4 Worth It? – Poco F4 Camera Review with Samples](https://techburner.in/poco-f4-worth-it-poco-f4-camera-review-with-samples/)
    * [
        
        iQOO Neo 6 Camera Samples and Review – Is it a Worthy One?](https://techburner.in/iqoo-neo-6-camera-samples-and-review/)
    * [
        
        Realme GT Neo 3 Performance & Gaming Test : Does it Worth 36K?](https://techburner.in/realme-gt-neo-3-performance-test/)
    * [
        
        iQOO Z6 Pro Camera Performance: Is It Worth It?](https://techburner.in/iqoo-z6-pro-camera-performance-is-it-worth-it/)
    * [
        
        Realme GT 2 Pro Camera Test with Samples: Microscopic Camera Worth it?](https://techburner.in/realme-gt-2-pro-camera-test/)

    * [
        
        Let’s See If You Can Score 8/10 In This “Shershaah” Quiz](https://techburner.in/lets-see-if-you-can-score-8-10-in-this-shershaah-quiz/)
    * [
        
        You Are A Real Player If You Can Score 8/10 In This Olympics 2020 Quiz](https://techburner.in/you-are-a-real-player-if-you-can-score-8-10-in-this-olympics-2020-quiz/)
    * [
        
        Let’s See How Much Do You Know About “The GOAT”: Messi Quiz](https://techburner.in/lets-see-how-much-do-you-know-about-the-goat-messi-quiz/)
    * [
        
        Let’s See If You Have The Correct “Vision” To Score In This Quiz](https://techburner.in/lets-see-if-you-have-the-correct-vision-to-score-in-this-quiz/)
    * [
        
        Let’s See If You Can Score 8/10 In This GTA Quiz](https://techburner.in/lets-see-if-you-can-score-8-10-in-this-gta-quiz/)

BurnerGuard: Privacy Policy
===========================

[](# "Share on Facebook")[](# "Tweet This Post")[](# "Pin This Post")[\[email protected\]](https://techburner.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

[](whatsapp://send?text=BurnerGuard:%20Privacy%20Policy%20https://techburner.in/burnerguard-privacy-policy/)[\[email protected\]](https://techburner.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Last updated July 20, 2022**

This privacy notice for Burner Digital Pvt. Ltd. (“**Company**,” “**we**,” “**us**,” or “**our**“), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share (“**process**“) your information when you use our services (“**Services**“), such as when you:

* Download and use our mobile application (Burner Guard), or any other application of ours that links to this privacy notice

* Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events

**Questions or concerns?** Reading this privacy notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://techburner.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS**

**_This summary provides key points from our privacy notice, but you can find out more details about any of these topics by clicking the link following each key point or by using our table of contents below to find the section you are looking for._**

**What personal information do we process?** When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process personal information depending on how you interact with Burner Digital Pvt. Ltd. and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. 

**Do we process any sensitive personal information?** We do not process sensitive personal information.

**Do we receive any information from third parties?** We do not receive any information from third parties.

**How do we process your information?** We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law.

**What are your rights?** Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean you have certain rights regarding your personal information. 

**How do you exercise your rights?** The easiest way to exercise your rights is by filling out our data subject request form available here: [https://techburner.in/apps-contact/](https://techburner.in/apps-contact/), or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

Want to learn more about what Burner Digital Pvt. Ltd. does with any information we collect? Send us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://techburner.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

1. [WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#infocollect)
2. [HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#infouse)
3. [WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#whoshare)
4. [HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#inforetain)
5. [WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#privacyrights)
6. [CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#DNT)
7. [DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#caresidents)
8. [DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#policyupdates)
9. [HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#contact)
10. [HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?](http://www.csgnetwork.com/htmlcodetest.html#request)

1. **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Personal information you disclose to us**

**_In Short:_** _We collect personal information that you provide to us._

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us.

User’s installed applications list is collected and used to detect harmful apps, we do not disclose installed applications list to anywhere, we do not store this information, we just collect and use it, Burner Guard provides option to delete the data.

**Application Data.** If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission:

* _Mobile Device Access._ We may request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s bluetooth, camera, microphone, storage, and other features. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.

This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

2. **HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent._

**We use accessibility API service in our app**: Due to growing privacy concerns about third-party apps and how often our camera or microphone is utilised. When an app accesses these features on your phone, Privacy Indicator attempts to fix the problem by displaying a little indicator on the screen. Burner Guard activates the Privacy Indicator feature by using the AccessibilityService API. With the aid of the AccessibilityService API, a Privacy Indicator is displayed on screen over every programme and screen, keeping track of permissions like Mic, Camera, or Location utilised by other third-party apps. When Burner Guard is closed or in the background, AccessibilityServiceAPI aids in the use of this feature.

**We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:**

3. **WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We may share information in specific situations described in this section and/or with the following third parties._

We may need to share your personal information in the following situations:

* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

4. **HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than 90 days.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

5. **WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_**  _You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

 If you are located in the EEA or UK and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority.

**Withdrawing your consent:** If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, which may be express and/or implied consent depending on the applicable law, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us.

However, please note that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal, nor when applicable law allows, will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at [\[email protected\]](https://techburner.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

6. **CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

7. **DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_** _Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information._

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g., backups, etc.).

8. **DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?**

**_In Short:_** _Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

9. **HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?**

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at [\[email protected\]](https://techburner.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

10. **HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?**

Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please visit: [https://techburner.in/apps-contact/](https://techburner.in/apps-contact/)

#### You May Also Like

 [ 

Top Stories2 years ago

Subscription Based Telegram Premium to Arrive This Month
--------------------------------------------------------

Telegram is yet another most popular messaging service after WhatsApp and Facebook Messenger worldwide. In 2021 October, WhatsApp and Facebook...](https://techburner.in/subscription-based-telegram-premium-to-arrive-this-month/) [ 

Top Stories2 years ago

Top 5 Windows Apps That You Should Try
--------------------------------------

Microsoft Windows 11 is packed with many new features that make it more fun and productive. To make your work...](https://techburner.in/top-5-windows-apps-that-you-should-try/) [ 

Gaming2 years ago

Best FPS Settings for Apex Legends Mobile
-----------------------------------------

When it comes to gaming, a good internet connection and good FPS matter the most. It’s been a few days...](https://techburner.in/best-fps-settings-for-apex-legends-mobile/) [ 

Gaming2 years ago

5 Tips to Reach Heroic Rank or Above in Free Fire MAX
-----------------------------------------------------

In gaming, the one with the highest rank is considered a pro. No matter the game whether it’s BGMI, Free...](https://techburner.in/5-tips-to-reach-heroic-rank-or-above-in-free-fire-max/) [ 

Gaming2 years ago

Free Fire MAX vs Apex Legends Mobile: Which One is Better?
----------------------------------------------------------

It’s been a few days since the launch of Apex Legends Mobile and people are enjoying the game. But there...](https://techburner.in/free-fire-max-vs-apex-legends-mobile-which-one-is-better/)

[

Software Update2 years ago

MIUI 14 Announced : What’s New, Features, and Devices List
----------------------------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/miui-14-announced-whats-new-features-and-devices-list/)[

Featured2 years ago

Google Pixel 7, 7 Pro Stock Wallpapers Download
-----------------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/google-pixel-7-7-pro-stock-wallpapers-download/)[

Featured2 years ago

Best TWS Under 3000 Rs in India to Buy
--------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/best-tws-under-3000-rs-in-india-to-buy/)[

Mobile2 years ago

Best 5G Smartphones Under 20000 in India
----------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/best-5g-smartphones-under-20000-in-india/)[

Featured2 years ago

Google Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro Launched
---------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/google-pixel-7-and-pixel-7-pro-launched/)

[

Guides2 years ago

Top 7 Photography Tricks Using Mobile Phone
-------------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/top-7-photography-tricks/)[

Bawal News3 years ago

What’s Inside Elon Musk Twitter Deal & Future Plans
---------------------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/whats-inside-elon-musk-twitter-deal-future-plans/)[

Gadgets3 years ago

Top 9 Cool And Weird Gadgets To Buy In 2022
-------------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/top-9-cool-and-weird-gadgets-to-buy-in-2022/)[

Bawal News3 years ago

Top 5 New Innovative Gadgets of 2022!
-------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/top-5-new-innovative-gadgets-of-2022/)[

Top Stories3 years ago

Top 10 Creative Ways To Reuse Your Old Smartphone
-------------------------------------------------](https://techburner.in/top-10-creative-ways-to-reuse-your-old-smartphone/)

Copyright © 2022 Burner Digital Pvt Ltd
